Ben: Hello, we have a reservation. The name is Ben Fischer.
Waiter: Yes, here we are. A table for two?
Ben: Yes, that’s right.
Waiter: OK, come this way.
Waiter: Are you ready to order?
Ben: Yes, I’ll have the soup and the mushroom ravioli, please.
Izzy: I’d like the mozzarella salad and then the chicken, please.
Ben: What would you like to drink?
Izzy: Just water for me.
Ben: A bottle of mineral water, please.
Waiter: Still or sparkling?
Ben: Is sparkling OK?
Izzy: Yes, sparkling.
Waiter: Perfect.
Ben: Thank you.
Izzy: Thank you.
Ben: Bon appetite!
Izzy: That is really good. Smells nice?
Ben: Yeah…
Izzy: Yeah really nice.
Waiter: How was your food?
Ben: It was great, thanks.
Izzy: Really delicious.
Waiter: Would you like a dessert?
Ben: No, thank you. Could we have the bill, please?
Waiter: Of course.
Ben: Thank you.